Guide to the Yale Daily News Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, 1957-1982; Series I
  - 1973
    - 1973 January 3-30
      - Mahevishna Orchestra, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Student's reactions to calendar change, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Draft, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Polo Horse, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 1973 February 1-28
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Freshman basketball v. Brown, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Polo v. Cornell, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Freshman Basketball, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Fencing v. Penn, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Track v. Cornell, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Wrestling v. Harvard, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Swimming v. Princeton, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Graduate Student Art Exhibition AandA building, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Grad. Student Senate, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Tow truck, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Teaching Curriculum, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Bicycle Accident, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Sit-up Contest, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Turkey, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Enthpy (?), 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Little Mary Sunshine, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Teaching Symposium, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Stiles Dramat-LUV, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Yale Christian Fellowship, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - SDS meeting, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 1973 March 2-13
      - Harvard Hockey, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Gymnastics, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Welcome Giants 1973 at Chapel Square Mall, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Signing of Sr. Fund Drive Petition, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Women's Basketball v. Manopers, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Evan's Silhouette/Track, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Calhoun Annex/Hillhouse Thermostat Mystery, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Volleyball, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Mickey Mouse, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Blood Drive, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Alderman, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Gloomy Dusk Scene, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Varsity Debate, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - 1973 April 1-30
      - Renaissance Fair Costumes, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Track in Florida, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Volleyball v. Springfield, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Varsity Baseball, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - V. Lacrosse v. Rutgers, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - V. Baseball v. Mt. Holyoke, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Lacrosse v. Dartmouth, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Tennis Doubles: Lee Gaines/Jeff Wilday, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Tennis v. Army, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Ethical Investment? Exxon Sign, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Tennis v. Cornell, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Baseball v. Cornell, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Boxing in Davenport, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Women's Demonstration-Woodbridge Hall, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Food-Meat (?) being served on the boycott, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Yale vs. BU crew, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Picasso- art gallery, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Varsity Light Weight Crew, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Talent show, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Boxing, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Whiffenpoof tap night, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - TD Charities Drive talent show, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - 1973 May 3-6
      - Vietnam teach-in, 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Women's Tennis Final Singles, 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Freshman Lacrosse, 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Freshman Baseball v. Princeton, 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - HYP Lightweight Cre, 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 1973 September 6-29
      - Osborne's Master's Swimming, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - FTBE Practice/Henning, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Football Scrimmage v. Dartmouth, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Football Dartmouth, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Soccer v. U of NH, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Track Star, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Soccer v. Amherst, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1973 October 1-20
      - Football v. Columbia, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Fairfield Rugby, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Football v. Colgate, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Yale Band; Colgate Football game, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Soccer, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Rugby v. Brown, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Football v. Brown, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Judy Dixon woman's tennis, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - New York giants vs. Green Bay Packers, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Giants vs. Redskins, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Trash bins for Ecology, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 1973 October 21-31
      - V Soccer v. Springfield, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Freshman Crew, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. S Conn, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Freshman Football v. Army, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Cross Country v. Cornell, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Soccer v. S. Conn, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Yale Med. School catalog, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Nixon impeachment meeting-common room, Calhoun, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Yale Graduate Students, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Alumni, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Alumni weekend, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Art gallery exhibition, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Garvan Collection-art gallery, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Halloween Pumpkin and misc., 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Symphony, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 1973 November 3-17
      - Rugby v. Manhattan, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Field Hockey v. Trinity, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Football v. Penn, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Rugby v. Penn, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Soccer v. Penn, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Field Hockey v. Redcliffe, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - V. Hockey v. Princeton, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Giants/Cowboys, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - 1973 November 17-28
      - Football v. Princeton, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Rugby v. Princeton, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Soccer v. Harvard, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - NCAA Soccer v. Bridgeport, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Hockey v. St. Nick's, 1973 November (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - 1973 December 1-18
      - Hockey v. Williams, 1973 December (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Squash v. Wesleyan, 1973 December (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Hockey v. U of Penn, 1973 December (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1973 December (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1973 December (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Yale Concert Band, 1973 December (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 1974
    - 1974 January 16-31
      - Hockey v. U Mass, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Fencing v. Johns Hopkins, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Swimming v. Montclair, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Swimming v. Stanford, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Hockey v. Clarkson, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Stanford Swim Meet, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Basketball v. Amherst, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Wrestling v. Rutgers, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Hockey v. Boston College, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Basketball v. Milton, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Tang Cup Scrimmage, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Poynter Panel, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Cubism-Yale Art Gallery, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Symposium at Law School, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Kung Fu, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Davenport Flag, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Women's basketball, 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - 1974 February 1-29
      - Basketball v. Mt Holyoke, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Mellon Fellowship Winners, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Fencing v. Radcliffe, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Hockey v. N Eastern, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Swimming v. Navy, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Swimming, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Wrestling v. U of Penn, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Hockey v. U Mass, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Wrestling v. Princeton, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Basketball v. Cornell, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Trumbull Hockey, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Women's Basketball v. Western Conn, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Wrestling v. BU, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - 8000 person to register at Payne Whitney, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Inquiring Photographer, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Course Critique Chair Count-LC, LS, SSS, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Judo, 2a chair, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - PU debate, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Yale Political Union Vote, 1974 February (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 1974 March 1-31
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Swimming v. Harvard, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Fencing v. Harvard, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Mellon Fellowship Winners, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Free-Throw contest awards presentation, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Tricycle race, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Charities Drive $1000 system-audio den, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Inquiring Photographer, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Grant education program, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Ads on campus, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Fire truck at Sterling, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Campus Scenes, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Travel show, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Symphony rehearsal, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Blake St. band, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Symphony, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Frisbee, baseball-the snow, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Summer term meeting, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - 1974 April 20 - May 30
      - Crew v. Penn and Columbia, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Rugby v. Manhattan, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Lacrosse v. Penn, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Crew v. Coast Guard, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Baseball v. Choate, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Lacrosse v. Williams, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Women's Tennis, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Crew v. Rutgers and N Eastern, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Baseball v. Penn, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Harvard Baseball, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Commencement roll, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Globetrotters, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - 1974 September 4-30
      - Football Practice, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Scrimmage v. Rutgers, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Soccer Practice, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Giants v. Patriots, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Soccer v. U of NH, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Cross Country v. U Conn, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Soccer v. U Conn, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Phelps Gate Banner: Welcome Class of 1978, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Trees, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Senior bash at Becton, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Beer can in Yale Bowl, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Cross campus rock festival- sunny day at Yale, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Redskins and Giants, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Cheerleader try-outs, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Whiffenpoofs of 1975, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Senior bash at Becton, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - CISL, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Bike Man- Old Campus Soccer, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Crime, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Calvin Hill Day Care Center fair, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Gallo wine bottles, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Girl's field hockey, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - 1974 October 1-12
      - Chris Dimson Tennis Cup, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Football v. Colgate, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Soccer v. Army, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Giants v. Falcons, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Women's Tennis, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Football Practice, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Intercollegiate Football, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Football v. Brown, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Summer term Montale megs (?), 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Barrister's Union at Law School, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - The new blue, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Pay check, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Zits medicine, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Libra Festival, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - 1974 October 12-31
      - Football v. Brown, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Debate v. Oxford, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Great Trumbull Rubbeny, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. S Conn, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - NE Women's Tennis Tournament, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Baker's Dozen at Hen Drive Hall, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Masters arts exhibit, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Cocktail party for alumni at Payne Whitney Gym, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Yale Tour, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Yale band at Battell Chapel, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Whiffenpoofs, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - PU debate, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Drippy show (8th Floor Morse Tower), 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Sterling Book Sale, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Ellison College Meeting Pierson, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Freshman squash 1974, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Conrad SLA, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Trumbull beer and bike, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Dining Hall worker, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Halloween Party, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - 1974 November 2-29
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Field Hockey Practice, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Football v. Penn, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Football v. Jets Giants, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Tennis Practice, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Field Hockey v. Princeton, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Seth Corey on Durfee Fire Escape, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Alumni at Cox Cage House, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Yale Jazz Ensemble-Sprague Hall, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - National Town meeting, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Blood Drive, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Election Day at one Old Elm Street-Firehouse, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - A Man For All Seasons (play)-Calhoun, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - The Cherry Orchard (play)-Saybrook, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - ½ empty dining hall, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Meter maid, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Tree climber on old Courtney Whitney, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Trumbull time, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Oil panel-also misc., 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Train to Harvard, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Beinecke plaza pep rally, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Poynter Panel, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Saybrook forum from Academic Pressure (2), 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Coffee cups, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Orange, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Gulf oil talk, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - DP Gilbert and Sullivan Show, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - 1974 December 3-17
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Women's Swimming v. Smith, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - ASA- Shumway story, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Cakes and cookies at Trumbull, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Encyclopedia Britannica at CCL, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - An Evening with Mark Twain at Davenport Dramat, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Carolers at Sterling, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - White House Called, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Russian/Slavic choruses Battell Chapel, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Christmas at Yale '74, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Christmas pictures at Hartford, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 1975
    - 1975 January 11-31
      - Branford and Common Room, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Basketball Practice, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Hockey v. Army, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Freshman Basketball, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Swimming v. Army, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Wrestling v. Brown, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Squash v. Dartmouth, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Campus Cop Car, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Women's Swimming, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Hockey Practice, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Freshman Hockey, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Swimming v. Aventin Calen, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Inquiring Photographer, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Hockey v. U Mass, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Basketball v. Lehigh, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Wrestling v. Springfield, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Fencing v. CCNY, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Fencing, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Women's Hockey v. West Haven, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Women's Swimming v. S. Conn, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Swimming v. Villanova, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Barton Reas at PU, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Concert at Sprague Hall, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Aikido Demonstration, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Weird animal at the New Haven Mall, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Campus security, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Figure skating, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Chair Show at Trumbull, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Locks on Campus, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Shirwood/Greek village, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Gymnastics, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - New Haven Jazz Festival (Gil Evans), 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - WIC Program, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Statues and things, 1975 January (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 1975 February 1-27
      - Women's Basketball v. UNH, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Wanted: Photographer ad for Hevlers, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Judo v. Temple, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Women's Hockey Practice, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Women's synchronized swimming, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Women's Hockey v. Taft, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. U of New Hampshire, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. Choate, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Basketball v. U Conn, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Basketball v. E. Conn, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Squash v. Princeton, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Basketball V. Harvard, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Wrestling v. Cornell, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Davenport Football, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Wrestling v. Harvard, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Gymnastics at Rutgers, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Wrestling v. BU, 1975 February (Box 5, Folder 56)